<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bookalot2</string>


    <string name="python">Learn to buand optild imize attractive, functional web sites forsmartphones
Today, mobile devices outnumber desktop and laptop computersthree to one. Skill in developing web sites that work on mobiledevices is in demand, and this friendly, step-by-step guide showshow to build and optimize sites using HTML5 and other standard webdevelopment tools.!</string>


    <string name="basiccomp">A neat twist that can be done with any of the new Teavana teas is called a tea latte.
    Basically, a tea latte is equal parts hot tea and steamed milk.  </string>


    <string name="c1">Starbucks Orange Mango Smoothie. A nourishing blend of natural orange mango juice,
    a whole banana, milk, whey protein, and fiber powder and ice.</string>


    <string name="codingfork">Vanilla Bean Crème Frappuccino® Blended Beverage. This rich and creamy blend of vanilla bean, milk and ice topped with
    whipped cream takes va-va-vanilla flavor to another level.</string>


    <string name="core">By Starbucks definition, a cappuccino is mostly milk foam, which weighs a lot less than milk. ... More specifically, a
    cappuccino is made up of shots of espresso, half steamed milk (2% by default,) </string>


    <string name="cplus">Thai Tea is is made from strongly-brewed black tea, often spiced with ingredients such as star anise,
    crushed tamarind, cardamom</string>
    <string name="java">Right next to water, tea is hailed as the most consumed drink in the world. Every single drop of tea
    comes from the same type of plant</string>
    <string name="php">Bubble Tea is the name given to the wide variety of refreshing flavoured
    fruit teas and milk teas served ice cold or piping hot with chewy
    tapioca balls that you suck up through a big fat straw! .</string>
    <string name="python2in1">Smooth and creamy matcha sweetened just right and served with steamed milk. This
    favorite will transport your senses to pure green delight. </string>
    <string name="pythononpro">Smooth and creamy matcha sweetened just right and served with steamed milk. This
    favorite will transport your senses to pure green delight. </string>
    <array name="streams">

        <item>Applications Development</item>
        <item>Communications Networking</item>
        <item>Multimedia Fundamentals</item>
        <item>Electives</item>
    </array>
</resources>